

# DANIEL FERNÁNDEZ

ANDROID AND JAVA DEVELOPER

INNOVATION AND MANAGEMENT
IN TOURISM

# PROFILE

Highly self-motivated Junior Developer committed to pursuing a career change in the IT sector. Offering 17 years of experience in tourism and hospitality, and having lived in different places, adapts quickly to changes and environments. Creative and flexible team player who enjoys learning new skills and expanding his knowledge.

# CONTACT

fernandez.daniel85@gmail.com +34 640782812 7 / February / 1985

Barcelona, Spain

# **►** LANGUAGES

Spanish, Catalan (Mother tongue)
English (Advanced - CAE)
German, Italian (Intermediate - A2)
Russian, French - (Basic - A1)

# SKILLS

Android, Java, Spring, MySQL, MongoDB HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Git (Intermediate) Firebase, Unity, 3DS Max, Inkscape (Basic) Opera PMS, Office (Advanced)

# **INTERESTS**

Travel, gastronomy, cycling, trekking, programming and new technologies.

# **EDUCATION**

# 2020 APPLIED VIRTUAL REALITY COURSE (250H)

November 2020 – Currently studying
Indústria 4.0 – Desenvolupament Local - Santa
Perpètua de Mogoda (Spain)

### 2020 JAVA BACKEND DEVELOPER COURSE (350H)

June 2020 - November 2020

IT Academy - Cibernàrium - Barcelona Activa (Spain)

### 2020 MASTER'S IN MOBILE APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT

September 2016 - January 2020

Universitat Oberta de Catalunya – UOC (Online)

# 2015 MASTER'S IN INNOVATION AND MANAGEMENT IN TOURISM

Septembre 2012 – February 2015

Salzburg University of Applied Sciences (Austria)

#### 2011 BACHELOR'S IN TOURISM STUDIES

Septembre 2006 - July 2011

**University of Girona (Spain)** 

#### 2009 BUSINESS MANAGEMENT COURSE (ERASMUS)

September 2008 - June 2009

Plantijn Hogeschool Antwerpen (Belgium)

# WORK EXPERIENCE

#### 2020 GUEST SERVICE @ THE SERRAS HOTEL BARCELONA (Spain)

April 2015 – February 2020

Lobby presence, reception, porter, parking and concierge tasks.

### 2019 CHAUFFEUR/CHASSEUR @ KULM HOTEL ST. MORITZ (Switzerland)

December 2018 – April 2019 (Winter Season)

Lobby presence, chauffeur, porter, parking and concierge tasks.

# 2015 VOLUNTEER @ BERLIN HOSTERIA (Ecuador)

August 2014 – January 2015

Landscaping, gardening, animal care, website and reservations system.

# 2014 F&B ATTENDANT @ NH SALZBURG CITY (Austria)

December 2012 - April 2014

Food & Beverage service at bar, restaurant, room service and meetings.

#### 2012 FRONT OFFICE @ SHERATON PRAGUE (Czech Republic)

November 2011 – September 2012

Front Office tasks, check-in, check-out, information, and problem solving.

#### 2011 FRONT OFFICE @ SHERATON AMSTERDAM (Netherlands)

February 2011 – July 2011

Front Office tasks, check-in, check-out, and information (Internship).

### 2011 F&B ATTENDANT @ HOTEL INDALO PARK (Spain)

Summers 2002 – 2011

Food & Beverage services at bar, lounge and terrace.